Guide to the Robert Hebb Records
Cary Institute of Ecosystem Studies
- 3 - Miscellaneous, 1972 - 1982
  - Greenhouse Emergency Training #1 - #5, undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda - 1979 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Fall Color Festival - 1978 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda - 1978 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda - 1976 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Memoranda - Prior 1976, 1974 - 1975 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Equipment Inventory, undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Budget - 1979/80 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Budget - 1977/78 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Budget - CETA, 1977 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Donations, 1977 - 1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Progress Reports - 1978/79, 1977 - 1980 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Monthly Reports - 1972/73, 1972 - 1973 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- 4 - Plant Acquisitions and Donations, 1976 - 1980
  Arranged chronologically.
  This series contains plant lists, correspondence, and memoranda pertaining to plant acquisitions, donations, and the distribution of surplus plant material. Additional folders originally in this series were given to the New York Botanical Garden.
  - Plants - Donated, Surplus, Distribution - 1975, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Plants - Donated, Surplus, Distribution - 1978, 1976 - 1979 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Plant Acquisitions - 1979, 1978 - 1979 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Plants - Donated, Surplus, Distribution - 1979, 1979 - 1980 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- 5 - Marshall & Stevens Tree Inventory, 1976 - 1979
  This series contains field books, survey sheets, and grid locations from inventories of plant material at the Cary Arboretum. The field books and survey sheets deal with material accessioned in the winter of 1976-1977, and are accompanied by an instruction manual developed by Marshall & Stevens, Inc. for analyzing, classifying, and creating a standardized inventory of major plant material. The grid locations detail inventories of tree collections taken between 1977 and 1979.
  - Field books & loose leaf, 1976 - 1977 (Box 13)
  - Instruction Manual - Plant Material Inventory, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Exposure Draft - Plant Material Inventory, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Survey sheets & copies, 1976 - 1977 (Box 14)
  - Survey sheets & copies, 1976 - 1977 (Box 15)
  - Grid Locations of Tree + Plant Survey, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Willow Collection, 1977 - 1978 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Birch Collection, 1977 - 1979 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Major Tree Avenue, 1977 - 1979 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Greenhouse, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Alder Collection, 1977 - 1979 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - A. Lovelace House Plantings, 1977 - 1979 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Ash Collection, undated (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - West Flagler Drive, 1977 - 1979 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Teahouse Rd. / Lovelace Dr., 1977 - 1978 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Poplar Collection, undated (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Plant Science Building, 1977 - 1979 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Pine Collection, 1977 - 1979 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Pecan/Fagus Collection, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Oak Collection, 1979 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Maple Collection, 1977 - 1979 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - L. Lovelace House Planting, undated (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Knapp House Planting, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Gifford House Planting, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Conover House Planting, 1977 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- 6 - Plant Inventory, 1975 - 1984
  This series contains lists of plants to be dug and planted, plant inventories for different locations at the Cary Arboretum, and lists of surplus plant material. Additional folders originally in this series were given to the New York Botanical Garden.
  Arranged by subject.
  - Planting/Digging List - Fall 1980 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Digging/Planting List - Spring 1982, 1981 - 1982 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Digging/Planting List - Spring 1983, 1983 - 1984 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Digging List - Fall 1983 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Planting List - Fall 1982 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Planting List - Spring/Fall 1981 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Greenhouse Inventory - Aug. 1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Greenhouse Inventory - Nov. 1978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Greenhouse Inventory - Nov. 1980 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Greenhouse Inventory - Oct. 1981 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Fern Case Inventory, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Greenhouse Inventory - Dec. 1982, 1982 - 1983 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Lath House Inventory - 1978 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Lath House Inventory - 1979 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Lath House Inventory - 1980 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Lath House Inventory - 1981 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Lath House Inventory - 1982 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1975 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1976, 1975 - 1976 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1978 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1979 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1980 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1981 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1982 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1983 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Nursery Inventory - 1984 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Spare Plants Distribution List, 1983 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Nursery Surplus Plants - Fall 1981 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Spare Plants List - Spring 1983 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Spare Plants - Fall 1982 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Spare Plants - Spring 1981 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Spare Plants - Fall 1980 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- 7 - Correspondence Copies, 1975 - 1977
  This series contains copies of memoranda and other correspondence.
  - June 1975 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - July-August 1975 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - September 1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - October 1975 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - November-December 1975 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - January-June 1976, 1975 - 1976 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - July-December 1976 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - January-June 1977, 1976 - 1977 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - July-October 1977 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- 8 - Correspondence, 1976 - 1984
  This series contains correspondence, memoranda, and a few miscellaneous items that were sent alongside the correspondence.
  - General Correspondence A - L, 1977 - 1984 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence M - Z, 1976 - 1984 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- 9 - Miscellaneous, 1973 - 1984
  This series contains miscellaneous correspondence, memoranda, and other administrative materials.
  - Taylor Lilac Arboretum, undated (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Rhododendron Dell, 1981 - 1982 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Longwood Gardens - Perennial Conference, 1981 - 1982 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Thank You Letters - Perennial Garden, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - IBM Atrium - Madison Ave., 1978 - 1984 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Member's Trip - Spring 1984, 1982 - 1984 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - AABGA - 1977, 1975 - 1979 (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - AABGA - Exhibitors (1982) (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Garden Club of America - Plants that Merit List, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Staff Directory, 1973 - 1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - TIAA, 1974 - 1976 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Union, 1979 - 1981 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Budget Requests - 1975-79, 1975 - 1978 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- 10 - Plants in Containers Project, 1974 - 1978; 1975
  This series contains photographs, correspondence, and field survey questionnaires from a survey of container-grown plants in urban spaces conducted in 1975. The study was financed by a grant from the National Endowment for the Arts with the goal of developing a manual of information about container planting.
  - Plants in Containers, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Notes - Container Project, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Container Project, 1975 - 1976 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller Plaza Area, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - NYU Housing Campus, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Tape Transcripts, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Grace Plaza, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Bibliography, undated (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Presentation Report 5/31/75, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence, 1975 - 1976 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Grant Application - NEA, 1974 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Battery Park Area - Photos, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - J. Bilbo Rooftop Garden, undated (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Beth Israel Halfway House, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Draft - Trees of NYC, 1976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Containers, 1975 - 1978 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Field Survey Questionnaires, 1975 (Box 23, Folder 17)